# Bassil Alqadi alqadi

Full stack web developer

Experienced Web Developer working in the Computer Software industry. Skilled in Soft Skills, Team Motivation, Computer Literacy, and Creativity Skills. Strong Frontend and Backend experience with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer and Information Systems from Yarmouk University



- bassilalqadi65@gmail.com
- ♀ Irbid, Jordan
- bassil-h.web.app/
- github.com/bassil-97

- 00962791858735
- # 27 June, 1997
- in linkedin.com/in/bassil-algadi-929164195

### **EDUCATION**

## BSc in Computer Information Systems.

Yarmouk University

09/2015 - 06/2019

Jordan, Irbid

# MSc in Computer Information Systems.

Yarmouk University

09/2020 - Present

Jordan, Irbid

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Web Developer Trainee Al-Hussain Technical University

06/2020 - 09/2020

Trainee – HTU (Hussain Technical University) National ICT upskilling program (340hrs), certified program from HTU University: · Technical (180 hrs.): o HTMLS. o CSS3. o JavaScript. o jQuery. o Bootstrap4. o MySQL. o PHP. o React.js o Node.js. · Soft Skills (60 hrs.): o Introduction to soft skills. o Smart goals and personal vision. o Johari windows and SWOT analysis. o Interpersonal communication. o Delivering presentation. o Team work and team building. o Job profile and setting interviews. · English (100 hrs.): o Reading and writing. o Listening. o Presentations. Conversations.

# Full stack web developer

Mostaql (Freelancer)

02/2021 - Present

## SKILLS

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

Reactis

PHP

Dealing with APIs

## PERSONAL PROJECTS

#### Bassil Alqadi Portfolio

- Personal website created using React.js library to describes my technical skills in developing websites. Including projects that I've worked on.
- https://bassil-h.web.app/

#### Covid-React.js tracker

- An application built using React.js library to track corona virus cases around the world. Also there are charts to describe information in visual way.
- cov-19-6a10e.web.app

#### Covid-Game

- An online game which used a True/False statements about corona virus information. Its created using React.js
- https://awo-d36e9.web.app/

#### Works Portfolio

https://mostagl.com/dashboard/portfolio

### **CERTIFICATES**

CCA-Certificate-HTML Level 1

CCA-Certificate-CSS Level 1

CCA-Certificate-Javascript Level 1

CCA-Certificate-jQuery Level 1

CCA-Certificate-MySQL Level 1

CCA-Certificate-PHP Level 1

## **LANGUAGES**

Arabic

Fnalish

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

### **INTERESTS**

web development

frontend

backend